No one believed in them. Except him.
The Ron Clark Story is a tv movie, drama film directed by Randa Haines.
Passionate and innovative teacher Ron Clark leaves his small
hometown to teach in one of Harlem's toughest schools.
But to break through to the students, he must use unconventional methods, including his
ground-breaking classroom rules, to help them reach their potential.
Based on a true story.
Ron Clark, played by Matthew Perry.
Shameika Wallace, played by Hannah Hodson.
Y'landa, played by C.J. Jackman-Zigante.
Hadley, played by Griffin Cork.
Marissa Vega, played by Melissa De Sousa.
Jason, played by Aaron Grain.
The Ron Clark Story (also known as The Triumph) is a 2006
American television film starring Matthew Perry.
The film is based on the educator Ron Clark.
It follows the tale of an idealistic teacher who leaves his small hometown to teach in a
New York City public school, where he faces trouble with the students.
The film was directed by Randa Haines, and was released directly on television, premiering on TNT on August 13, 2006 and
was later released on DVD in the 10 Movie Kid's Pack Volume 3 by Echo Bridge Home Entertainment in 2011.
The film explores themes of biography, teacher,
woman director, enthusiastic, gentle.
The tone is emotional.